{
   "quiz_1" : [
       {
          "question" : "Where is Albany?",
          "answer" : "New York",
          "choices" : ["New York","New Jersey","Florida","California"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is New York."
       },
       {
           "question" : "Where is Trenton?",
           "answer" : "New Jersey",
           "choices" : ["New York","New Jersey","Florida","California"],
           "feedback" : "Correct answer is tens New Jersey."
        },
        {
          "question" : "Where is Dallas?",
          "answer" : "Texas",
          "choices" : ["New York","New Jersey","Florida","California"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is Texas."
        },
       {
           "question" : "Where is Los Angeles?",
           "answer" : "California",
           "choices" : ["New York","New Jersey","Florida","California"],
           "feedback" : "Correct answer is California."
       }
      {
          "question" : "What country is Paris in?",
          "answer" : "France",
          "choices" : ["France","Mexico","Italy","Russia"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is France."
       },
       {
           "question" : "What country is Guadalajara in?",
           "answer" : "Mexico",
           "choices" : ["France","Mexico","Italy","Russia"],
           "feedback" : "Correct answer is Mexico."
        },
        {
          "question" : "What country is Rome in?",
          "answer" : "Italy",
          "choices" : ["France","Mexico","Italy","Russia"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is Italy."
        },
       {
           "question" : "What country is Moscow in?",
           "answer" : "Russia",
           "choices" : ["France","Mexico","Italy","Russia"],
           "feedback" : "Correct answer is Russia."
       },
      {
          "question" : "What country is Barcelona in?",
          "answer" : "Spain",
          "choices" : ["Spain","Mexico","Colombia","Chile"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is Italy."
        },
       {
           "question" : "What country is Bogota in?",
           "answer" : "Colombia",
           "choices" : ["Spain","Mexico","Colombia","Chile"],
           "feedback" : "Correct answer is Russia."
       }     
       ],
   "quiz_two" : [
       {
          "question" : "What is 1+1?",
          "answer" : "2",
          "choices" : ["2","3","4","5"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is 2."
       },
       {
           "question" : "What is 2+2?",
           "answer" : "4",
           "choices" : ["1","2","3","4"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is 4."
        },
       {
           "question" : "What is 3+3?",
           "answer" : "6",
           "choices" : ["2","4","6","8"],
           "feedback" : "Correct answer is 6."
  
        },
      {
          "question" : "What is 4+4?",
          "answer" : "8",
          "choices" : ["2","4","6","8"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is 8."
      },
      {
          "question" : "What is 5+5?",
          "answer" : "10",
          "choices" : ["5","10","15","20"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is 10."
       },
       {
           "question" : "What is 6+6?",
           "answer" : "12",
           "choices" : ["3","6","9","12"],
           "feedback" : "Correct answer is 12."
        },
        {
          "question" : "What is 7+7?",
          "answer" : "14",
          "choices" : ["7","14","21","28"],
          "feedback" : "Correct answer is ."
        },
       {
           "question" : "What is 8+8?",
           "answer" : "16",
           "choices" : ["8","16","24","32"],
           "feedback" : "Correct answer is 16."
   }
]
